Guide to the James Emerson Lindsey Papers 1926-1972
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections
James Emerson Lindsey Papers
1926-1972
1931-1934
Washington State University Libraries, Manuscripts, Archives, and Special Collections Pullman, WA, 99164-5610 USA (509) 335-6691 http://www.wsulibs.wsu.edu/masc mascref@wsu.edu
Cage 491
Lindsey, James Emerson
.25 feet of linear shelf space 1 box
This collection consists of biographical sketches of Whitman County, Washington and Latah County, Idaho pioneers recorded by James Emerson Lindsey in 1931 and 1934.
This collection consists of biographical sketches of Whitman County, Washington and Latah County, Idaho pioneers recorded by James Emerson Lindsey in 1931 and 1934. Significant individuals include Daniel Wright Boone, William H. Brabyn, Walter A. Fiscus, Oliver R. Hall, John Morris Klemgard, Christian Naffziger, George E. Ritchey, and Carson W. Taylor. These sketches include information about family origin, spouse and children, life achievements, and miscellaneous information.
Additional materials about George E. Ritchey include a newspaper clipping dating from 1926 and a memorandum from 1972.
The collection is arranged alphabetically in a single series.
This collection is open and available for research use.
Boone, Daniel Wright, -- 1885-1936; Brabyn, William H., -- 1853-; Fiscus, Walter A., -- 1880-; Hall, Oliver R., -- 1852-1946; Klemgard, John Morris, -- 1873-; Naffziger, Christian, -- 1884-; Ritchey, George E., -- 1870-
Frontier and pioneer life -- Idaho -- Latah County; Frontier and pioneer life -- Washington (State) -- Whitman County
Washington (State); Idaho; Pioneers
- Andrew Anderson, Jr., 1931 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Joseph C. Baird, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Daniel Wright Boone, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- William H. Brabyn, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Joseph R. Collins, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Samuel Easto, circa 1934 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- George W. Ellis, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Walter A. Fiscus, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Nicholas E. J. Gentry, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Walter Scott Getchell, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Walter C. Glaspey, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Oliver Hall, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Martha Estes Hawley, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Vincent L. Higgins (2 copies), 1934 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Frederick A. Hodges, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Mary Catherine Byrd Johnson, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 16)
- David R. Judson and Lucy Ann Judson Grant, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- Charles O. Kellogg, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- John Morris Klemgard, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- James E. Lindsey, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Mrs. C. R. Moys (Emma D. Croyle), 1934 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Christian Naffziger, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- George A. Northrup, circa 1934 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Augusta R. Bott Peer, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 24)
- George William (Billy) Reed, circa 1934 (Box 1, Folder 25)
- George E. Ritchey: newspaper clipping, biographical sketch, memorandum, and notes, 1926, 1934, 1972, undated (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Peter William Struppler, circa 1934 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Mrs. Jervis D. Swannack (Walula Elliott Hardy), circa 1934 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Carson W. Taylor, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Thomas J. Torpey, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Henry I. Willis, 1934 (Box 1, Folder 31)